Richard hi thanks so much for taking the
time out and joining us let me start by
asking you about a sector that was one
of the top gainers in trade today that's
Nifty realy now you had a bunch of
stocks in that sector like Phoenix Mills
orito realy Prestige Estates and so but
they've seen a good runup today and in
the last few days as well so do you see
any more upside for this sector going
ahead uh how do you see the realy sector
planning
out yes hi very good afternoon well if
you look at the broader markets then
since last few days the broader markets
have doing well and especially that
19,500 was the immediate resistance
which has been surp was surpassed with
The Gap up today now if you look at the
F positions about 80% of the positions
as on yesterday was still on the short
side and with Market continuing its
momentum it's quite likely that some of
this much of the short positions could
come to cover so in such case we could
see some further short covering move on
the index and know on the Nifty we
expect
19,7 700 would be the initial hurdle
tomorrow and once this 19 700 is pass
then I think 19850 could be the range
where markets could head so roughly
around 19,800 850 is where know we would
advise the traders to start some profit
booking but still for now the trend the
short-term Trend or the momentum Still
Remains
positive the shortterm trend remains
positive that's the word coming in from
RIT hi good afternoon rid this is Lisa
on the other side well we are seeing
Nifty it's going strong even the midcap
small cap they are quite excited so what
are the SE ctors or stocks that you are
betting in any coming in from the midcap
or small small cap
space yeah very good afternoon Lisa so
couple of recommendations both on the
long side first is a buy call in hindal
so Prim the metal specific metal
companies should do well because we have
seen that know the dollar Index have
started coming down and the fall in the
dollar Index is usually positive for the
metal stocks since they have inverse
correlation So hindalco within this
space is looking quite positive because
the stock has given a breakout of it
swing High Resistance that is that is
supported by better than average volume
so vindo can be bought for shortterm
with stop L 490 expecting Target
somewhere around 530 and ICC lombar is
one stock technically looking quite
positive consolidation has been seen
since last couple of months which just
seem to be a time wise correction within
an uptrend it's on the verge of a
breakout but we are just preempting that
breakout looking at the price volume
action so one can go long at current
levels and know if it gives a breakout
about 1320 then and sorry 1420 then one
can add more positions over there keep a
stop L below 1350 on the long positions
and expect Target somewhere around
1417 all right hindalco and ICI Lombard
a long positive view coming in from rich
rich thanks so much for taking the time
out and joining us today